the extra today woke up without a
el extra hoy amaneció sin cuenta de
Twitter account Okay What happened to Electra
Twitter Okay Qué ha pasado con Electra
while she woke up without a
mientras que amaneció sin cuenta de
Twitter account let's see I open pools of Whose
Twitter a ver abro porras de Quién ha
fault was it come on I
culpa venga yo
trust Whose fault was it come on
confío de Quién ha sido la culpa venga
you guys can
que ustedes podéis
almost come on Javi well well how did
casi venga de Javi bien bien cómo lo
you
habéis
know how did you know Javi's it
sabido cómo lo habéis sabido de Javi ha
was the
sido la
fault they suspended
culpa han suspendido la cuenta de
Electra's account the most neutral person there was It
Electra la persona más neutral que
seems that Javi Oliveira is
había Parece ser que a Javi oliveira le
bothered by the fact that there are people creating their
molesta que haya gente creando sus
own space when Electra got along
propios space cuando Electra se llevaba
well with the piss and many haters
bien con los pis y muchos haters la
hated her her account was great she fights
odiaban su cuenta estaba joya se pelea
with Javi and
con Javi y pasa
this happens you realize that the laser acts
esto te das cuenta que el laser actúa
as passive aggressive with you and always
como pasivo agresivo contigo y siempre
tries to humiliate you and is only happy about
trata de humillarte y solo se alegra de
the tragedy of others You think she is
la tragedia de otros Tú crees que es
someone normal or has an obsession I am not
alguien normal o tiene obsesión yo no
going to go into assessing her
voy a entrar en valorar su su tema
clinical issue okay that the sabral but passive
clínico vale eso el sabral pero a pasivo
aggressive No he is chasing
agresivo No él va persiguiendo aparecen
the tweets appear I see it appear in twit that I
los tweet me lo veo aparecer en twit que
gave it is here in my twit you know in my twit it
di es aquí en twit mío sabes en twit mío
is like  I don't understand but well as long as he
es como no lo entiendo pero bueno yo con
pays me what he owes me it's
que me pague lo que me tiene que
fine for me you understand me I mean I
pagar me va bien me entiendes o sea
hope it's already March I can't wait
espero que ya estamos en marzo no veo el
but I hope his
día pero espero que ya le llegue su
lawsuit arrives And once his
demanda Y una vez que le llegue su
lawsuit arrives, file the next one I mean there's
demanda ponerle la la siguiente o sea es
no more better This is what
que tampoco hay más vale Esto es lo que
happens when Javi Oliveira calls you so they
pasa cuando Javi oliveira te marca para
learn the difference between a
que aprendan la diferencia entre un
group that tells the
grupo que decimos la
truth and the other that is totally
verdad y el otro que está totalmente
sick and obsessed with doing harm
enfermo y obsesionado con hacer daño
The question would be that he is not
La pregunta sería de que no es
guilty Well I don't
culpable Pues no lo
know what a coincidence don't you think one day Javi
sé qué coincidencia no crees un día Javi
threatens Eltra with sending her a tweet and
amenaza a eltra con tirarle un tweet y
a few days later they delete his account
unos días después le borran la cuenta
Electra after Javi wouldn't stop
Electra después de que Javi No parase de
talking about her that is true this
hablar de ella eso eso sí es verdad este
meme is true eh I mean instead of taking down
meme es verdad eh o sea en vez de tirar
the accounts of real cosadores
las cuentas de verdaderos cosadores
we are going to start taking down the extra
nos vamos a poner a tirarlo del extra
well anyway eh Oh look here there is a
bueno en fin eh Ah mira que aquí hay una
compilation too I hadn't seen it
recopilación también no lo había visto
total alert the pambiitos and followers
alerta total los pambisitos y seguidores
of Javi Oliveira have taken down the
de Javi oliveira han tumbado la cuenta
extra's account the extra will come out to say that
del extra el extra saldrá a decir que
Javi has nothing to do with it although all  we
Javi no tiene nada que ver aunque todos
know that when the extra gets along
sabemos que sí cuando el extra se lleva
with them we have
bien con los este lo hemos
read it was not enough for him to make her remove the
leído no le bastó con hacerla quitar la
publication now he took away her account
publicación ahora le quitó la cuenta
pambisitos and kids have been
pambisitos y chavalería llevan
reporting us Now it is time to demonize and
reportándonos Ahora toca demonizar y
censor fight with the most
censurar pelearse con la gente más
normal people on the internet well deserved
normal de internet bien merecido que se
it How dare he criticize the churra the
lo tiene Cómo Osa criticar al churra al
psycho boss and his sect Well the
psicop patrón y su secta Bueno pues la
truth is
verdad es
that the extra called me in the afternoon
que me llamó el extra por la tarde me
the extra called me in the
llamó el extra por la
afternoon I think she realized
tarde yo creo que ella se dio cuenta
late that her account had been suspended
tarde que le habían suspendido la cuenta
eh I think the last thing she tweeted
eh Me parece que lo último que twite
because I happened to see it last night was something
porque casualmente lo vi anoche fue algo
like I'm going to watch a movie or something like that and she
como voy a ver una peli o algo así y me
called me in the afternoon and she was
me llamó por la tarde y me estuvo
telling me that as I already told her
comentando que como bien ya le dije yo
when I told her several times Because I
cuando le dije varias veces Porque
also told her eh I think I told her
además se lo dije eh creo que se lo dije
twice in space but she kept rqr
dos veces en space pero ella seguía rqr
no that neither Dallas nor miare nor I
no que ni Dallas ni miare ni yo le
were sending her clips that there is a
estábamos tirando clip que hay una
person Now that she is dedicating herself to
persona Ahora que se está dedicando a
reporting clips fraudulently not
reportar clips de manera fraudulenta no
filling out and well and miare's mother started
rellenando y bueno y se puso la madre de
and she and a few others to say look look
miare y ella y unos cuantos a decir mira
look why it says Francisco Javier
mira mira porque pone Francisco Javier
Oliveira and Daniel Santomé they are
oliveira y pone Daniel santomé son ellos
they are putting an address
son ellos están poniendo una dirección
in Barcelona that I am not going to throw anything away
de Barcelona que yo no voy a tirar nada
that I am not throwing anything away but the thing is that I don't know
que yo no tiro nada pero es que ya no sé
how to say it anymore in English I don't
cómo decirlo de verdad en inglés I don't
throw
tirar
anything away okay erion yoru Thank you very much,
Nothing vale erion yoru Muchísimas
the clear one is definitely involved this is part of the soc of the
el claro esto es parte de la soc de la
soc of malitos there is no more I mean I don't
soc de malitos no hay más O sea yo ya no
know how to tell her that I am not going to throw away
sé cómo decirle que yo no voy a tirar
a [ __ ] thing why am I going to throw
una [__] [__] para qué voy a tirar
anything away I mean what do I gain by throwing anything away well
nada O sea qué gano yo con tir nada pues
what are they space that talk about me Okay
qué son space que hablan de mí Bueno
so we go in pape we play I don't know I'll tell
pues entramos pape jugamos yo que sé ya
you Well Anyway she was telling me
te digo Bueno Total que me estuvo
that like they had thrown
que como que como que le habían tirado
the clif fraudulently at her and Twitter
los clif fraudulentamente y Twitter le
had
había
asked her to send her an email well
pedido que yo le mandara un email bueno
that the people of the clicks that they
que los la gente de los click que le
had sent her such no The Owners of the
habían mandado tal no Los Dueños del
content send her an email as if to
contenido le mandá demos un email como
say we have no problem with
diciendo no tenemos ningún problema con
this content I don't know that I don't know how much so well
este contenido no sé que no sé cuánto
I have sent her the email
entonces pues yo le he mandado el email
that she has asked me to send and that's it I
que ella me ha pedido que que mande y ya
hope it helps you know I  She said
está Espero que le sirva Sabes Me dijo
that she was going to ask Miare's mother
que ella se lo iba a pedir a la madre de
since she has followed her now since
miare como ahora la ha seguido como
Miare's mother has followed her, well she is
ahora la ha seguido la madre de miare
going to ask her, okay, so
pues se lo va a pedir vale para que
Miare sends her an email also
miare le mande un un email también
saying, Hey, I didn't throw the
diciendo Oye yo no le he tirado los
clips. Okay, and to cell and to c, okay too.
clips Vale y a cel y a c también vale
Then I'll go, I hope they return it to her.
Entonces voyar espero que se lo
Okay, what's
Vale qué es lo que
going on, my Are's mother already
pasa ya la madre de mi are ya se lo
sent it. All that's missing is cell. Well, that's it, she
envió Solo falta cel pues ya está se lo
will send it to her cell and that's
mandará cel y ya
it. There are many people who have told me
está que hay mucha gente que me ha dicho
I wouldn't give her anything, but well, no, I didn't
yo no le daría nada pero bueno no no
think that I haven't, many people have told me.
pensé que yo no me lo ha dicho mucha
Eh, no, no, don't do it. But because
gente Eh no no no lo hagas Pero porque
I don't want anyone's account to be closed.
yo no quiero que le cieren la cuenta a
No, but well, let's see if they
nadie no pero bueno a ver si a ver si se
know the one about
saben la de la de
rectifying these people. Do you think they are going to
rectificar esta gente creéis que van a
rectify or not? Well, of
rectificar o no rectifican pues
course,
claro
clear enough intelligence to understand
claro neidad suficiente para entender
for yourself, for Nimu and Ra, I
por ti solito por a nimu y a ra le
criticize them more harshly than
critico con más dureza que a
Dallas, of course, of course. It's not that nobody
Dallas claro supuesto No es que nadie lo
understands, no matter how much you tell me,
entiende por más que vos me digas lo que
nobody understands, I mean, I
me digas nadie lo entiende o sea yo
understand.  look you have 270 right now
entiendo mir tenés ahora mismo 270
you think they understand you but the rest
sueres que si te entienden pero el resto
of the world doesn't the rest of the world doesn't
del mundo no el resto del mundo no
understand
entiende
okay I'll tell you a
vale os cuento un
gossip let's see the story is let's see tell
chisme a ver la historia es a ver
me the gossip happens I was
cuéntame el chisme
talking to one of the
pasa estuve hablando con con uno de los
pambisitos Yeah that they put together these
pambisitos Ajá que que montan las
gatherings with
tertulias estas con
cen I was talking to one of the
cen estuve hablando con uno de los
pambisitos that put together these spaces that
pambisitos que montan las los space
make cel in which the
estos que hace cel en los que van los
pambisitos go and
pambisitos y
such And he says to me but where were you
tal Y me dice pero dónde estabas
yesterday and he says but where were you yesterday
ayer y me dice pero dónde estabas ayer
why didn't you
por qué no
come and
viniste y
I because I was sleeping it
yo porque estaba durmiendo
was [ __ ] early in the morning what do you expect I'm a
era de [__] madrugada qué esperas soy un
man who
señor que
works I mean I don't know when
trabaja o sea yo no sé cuándo van a
these things are going to happen and logically I have to
pasar estas cosas y lógicamente yo tengo
sleep besides and he says to me and I say
que dormir además y me dice y le digo
but you guys are [ __ ] and he says
pero sois unos cabrones y me dice Por
Why and I say because when I want to
qué y digo porque cuando yo quiero
put together the gatherings none of you come
montar las tertulias no venís ninguno
but but then the montcel and you all go
pero pero luego las montcel y vais todos
[ __ ]
cabrones
put them together cel and you all go there to
las monta cel y vais todos allí a
set it up and mess things up
montarla y a liarla
Oh and I
Oh y
say and  He
digo y me
tells me that they don't want to debate
dice es que no quieren debatir
with you so there there I like Dre
contigo así que ahí ahí me gusta Dre
Maria there I like Dream Maria Thank you
María ahí me gusta Dream María Gracias
for those
por esos
vitals I say I say of course they don't want to debate
vitaz digo digo claro no quieren debatir
with me because they know that they look
conmigo porque es que saben que quedan
bad their
mal su
egg and concel doesn't argue with them
huevo y concel no les discute
so much it's an
tanto es un
egg let's see what he says Who said that
huevo a ver qué dice Quién dijo eso
eh a friend of
eh un amigo
yours the one who can't be named no you can't
tuyo el que no se puede nombrar no no se
name
puede nombrar a
Javi is here a friend of yours a friend of
Javi está aquí un amigo tuyo un amigo
yours from Andalusia I don't know him
tuyo andaluz no sé
And if he wants to go up and explain that
el Y si quiere subir y explicar que
position is false false as always s is
puesto falso falso como siempre s está
live he is live he is here he is
en directo está en directo está aquí
here
está aquí
listening to who You are invited jis Who
escuchando qui Estás invitado jis Quién
wants to talk jisus
quiere hablar jisus
go ahead, even though I am not I am not a
adelante yo a pesar de que no soy no soy
Trader I mean if I have had
Trader O sea si he tenido carteras de
crypto wallets and such if I can or the space
cripto y demás si puedo o sea el espacio
so much that he knows and doesn't know about those of the
tanto que conoce y desconoce de los de
for scam and can can take
por estafa y puede puede tomar no muy
the subject not very well it's that it
bien el tema
's smoke Why Because we already
del es que es humo Por qué Porque ya nos
see each other host And this is tremendous eh
vemos [__] Y esto es tremendo eh
exactly they will do just I mean they
exactamente haran justamente o sea
were debating like with this
estaban debatiendo como con esta
chick the fact that in my time we
pava el hecho de que en mi tiempo se
fought to be able to choose not to shave our
luchase por poder elegir no depilarnos
armpits And  that now they make us
el sobaco Y que ahora nos hagan
shave all the hair on our body is
depilarnos todos los pelos del cuerpo es
a very good example of what has
un ejemplo muy bueno de que es lo que ha
happened in recent years with the
pasado en los últimos años con la lucha
feminist struggle, incredible, no I mean, incredible,
feminista increíble no O sea increíble
incredible
increíble
reflection and It seems that this
reflexión y Parece ser que es que esta
girl, okay, she's from the Win
chica vale que es la del programa de Win
michu show, this one that has a card show, no,
michu este que tiene de de cartas no
this girl has a show with Win
esta chica tiene un programa con Win
michu, some events with Win michu and things
michu unos eventos con Win michu y cosas
like that, I've never seen it, eh No, no, I don't know
así no lo he visto nunca eh No no no sé
exactly, I don't get it, I haven't
exactamente no le Pillo el rollo no le
finished asking the girl for the show,
he terminado de pedir el rollo a la
I mean, no, the
chica digo no el
show, well, it turns out that this
programa bueno Pues resulta ser que esta
girl
chica
has tweeted some
ha tuiteado unas cositas un poco
naughty things exactly jvan,
traviesas exactamente jvan justamente
I would say that this is a hater, uh, I'm not
diría que esta es hater Eh no estoy
sure, but her name sounds familiar from having
seguro pero me suena su nombre de
seen her throwing ha, it seems to me, it sounds familiar to me,
haberla visto tirando ha me parece me
yes, I think super hater, really
suena sí s creo que super hater cre
hater, this is not only that she saw the
hater esto ya no solo es que vio las
Twitch rules, saying this kind of
normas de Twitch decir esta clase de
things on Twitter, but it is
cosas en Twitter sino que es
directly illegal, I mean, at the legal level,
directamente ilegal O sea a nivel ley
this is very strong and to go to
esto es muy fuerte y para entrar en
prison, let's see, look at the tweet she
prisión dicea a ver fijaros el tweet que
posted about Dallas, eh, you do drugs, yes, and your
puso sobre Dallas eh Te drogas sí Y tu
mom knows, yes, and you  says nothing no
mamá lo sabe sí y no te dice nada no
because that drug does me good seriously
porque esa droga me hace bien en serio
what's it called I want to try it imagine
Cómo se llama quiero probarla imaginarse
Dallas dead in 1 different and
a Dallas muerto de 1 formas distintas y
painful ways It never fails eh I mean everything everything
dolorosas No falla eh o sea todo todo lo
that they have to do and and all the
que tengan que ver y y todas las
relationships and all the people that they get
relaciones y todo la gente con la que se
involved with is this type and that puts these
unten es de este tipo y que pone estas
things to Dallas but very very very it's that
cosas a Dalas pero muy muy muy es que
surely this is him it's the pass
seguramente esto es el es el el pase
surely this was the flyer to
seguramente este fue el flyer para
enter strong Honestly it should be
entrar fuerte Honestamente está para
reported on twich it's not even half normal to
reportar twich no es ni medio normal
start wishing me death on Twitter I
ponerse a desearme la muer en Twitter o
mean it's another level eh a person that you don't
sea es otro nivel eh una persona que no
know another exaggerated level I'm going to
conoces otro nivel exagerado yo lo voy a
report it because this is another level I mean imagine
reportar porque esto es otro nivel o sea
imagine because I don't know It's that
imaginaos imaginaos porque no s Es que
the chicka acts like a feminist because you
la tipa se las da de feminista porque ti
some things but then they get
algunas cosas pero es que luego se
scandalized by the Dallas clip on
escandalizan con el clip de Dallas en en
starde or not which is obviously not the
starde o no que evidentemente no es el
best clip No it's not the most
mejor clip No no es lo más
beautiful I can't believe that this is
bonito no me lo puedo creer que esto es
like this I mean this guy has done a live
así O sea este tipo ha hecho un directo
saying that the thing about the extra account is
diciendo que lo de la cuenta de extra es
mine jav oliveira with his community they make
mía jav oliveira con su comunidad hacen
massive reports it's terrible  things like I have
reportes masivos está fatal cosillas en
no idea his
plan del estilo No tengo idea su oración
political position but imagine if
política pero imaginos que esto lo
a man did this A man would do that
hicera un hombre Un hombre se pusiera
the balls he says I
con esas cosas los [__] de dice No
have no idea his
tengo idea de su orientación
political orientation you need to open the envelope
política hace falta abrirle el sobre
another streamer on her Twitter what they would
otra streamer en su Twitter lo que le
say to her and the girl says imagine giving you
dirían y la tía pone imaginarse a daras
in a thousand different and painful ways
de mil formas distintas y dolorosas
I want you to see it carefully what it
quiero que lo veis bien fijados lo que
says and the things that she has dedicated
pone y la de cosas que me ha dedicado
to me How horrible the name sounded familiar to me
Qué horror a mí me sonaba el nombre
because she saw a role-playing urona and I said it
porque vio de urona rolera y dije me
sounds familiar to me the girl wants me to die
suena de algo la tía me desea la mu de
constantly for years and that she hits me or I
constante durante años y que me pegue o
mean it's exaggerated eh it's exaggerated I'm
sea es exagerado eh es exagerado yo lo
going to report it Honestly I'm going to
voy a reportar Honestamente voy a
report it on Twitch this is a level of
reportar en Twitch esto es un nivel de
harassment another level be imagine Put it in a
acoso otro nivel sea imagin lo Pon de
thousand ways you feel painful And this
mil formas sientas dolorosas Y esto no
is not allowed on Twitch how strong eh
está permitido en Twitch qué fuerte eh
one thing that doesn't fall to you a person that you don't
una cosa que no te ca una persona que no
like their videos and you think it's me I
te gusten sus vídeos y te parezca una mi
have no problem telling us they are
yo tengo ningún problema que diganos son
terrible no problem nothing happens
malísimos ningún problema no pasa nada
Even if you feel like giving your opinion that you don't like me
Incluso si te apetece opinar que te
as a person no  It's okay, it's okay,
caigo mal como persona no pasa nada no
everyone has opinions on
pasa nada cada uno tiene opiniones para
whatever, you know It's okay, but
lo que sea sabes No pasa nada pero
wishing me dead, that they beat me up for
desearme la muerte que me peguen durante
years is exaggerated, it's exaggerated Look, he
años es exagerado es exagerado Mira me
's listening to me, he's listening to me,
está escuchando me está me está
Ah, because then he
escuchando Ah porque ya luego se da
realizes, no, that he comes in, I mean, but they're
cuenta no que él Entra o sea pero son
all the same, eh, she should be in
todos igual eh debería estar en la
jail, she's a stalker, she says, dala, but I mean, it's like, to, to, to be
cárcel es acosadora dice dala pero o sea
able to hang out
es como para para para poder juntarte
with those people, to be able to hang out
con esa gente para poder poder juntarte
with those people, it's like you have to
con esa gente es como que tienes que
pass that requirement, not to be in bad shape
pasar ese requisito no de estar fatal
with Dallas, not to say that you
con el Dallas no de ponerle que lo
want to kill him or something like that. Well, in
quieres Matar o algo de eso Bueno de
fact, I'm reminded of Vietnam.
hecho se me viene el recuerdo de Vietnam